ojcommerce.com 2019-10-05

# Furniture, Home Goods, Appliances, Athletic Gear, Fitness, Toys, Baby Products, Musical Instruments - OJCommerce.com

**Privacy Policy**

At OJCommerce your privacy is as important to us as it is to you. Our Customer Personal Information Privacy Policy defines how OJCommerce protects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes:

  * Why we collect personal information
  * What personal information we collect and when it is collected
  * How your information is used and protected
  * When and with whom your information is shared
  * What to do if you feel your personal information has been compromised

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services and websites offered by OJCommerce and affiliated companies. This Website is also governed by its Terms of Use. If any of the terms of this Privacy Policy directly conflict with the Terms of Use, the terms of this Privacy Policy will apply.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our Website or write to us at: [info@ojcommerce.com](mailto:info@ojcommerce.com)

This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information, which is information that OJCommerce collects from you as a customer that specifically identifies you as an individual. This information is collected to provide you with the products and services you have requested as well as to provide a pleasant shopping experience now and to improve the shopping experience in the future.

While we limit the information we collect, we do collect Personal Information when you: 

  * Place an order from our website
  * Create an account on our website
  * Return an item, make an exchange or submit a rebate
  * Inquire about our products or services or contact customer service
  * Receive a gift package
  * Sign up for OJCommerce email updates or other promotional materials
  * Enter a contest or sweepstakes
  * Are referred to us through a marketing promotion
  * Participate in a marketing survey, promotion or event

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect Personal Information including: 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Telephone number
  * Fax number
  * Email address
  * Transaction information
  * Credit card, debit card, or checking account information
  * Driver’s license number (in conjunction with merchandise returns)

In order to provide you with a better shopping experience and to improve the quality of our services, we may combine the information you submit under your account with other information that we may receive from you, from third parties, or with other public demographic information. We maintain this information, along with a record of your purchases, in a restricted database.

Also, our Website is not directed at collecting Personal Information from children and we do not actively collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13.

**What does the OJCommerce Privacy Policy cover?**

This privacy policy outlines OJCommerce practices regarding information collected online at www.OJCommerce and any other websites operated by the Company. We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. This policy was last revised on January 24, 2010. By visiting the Sites or otherwise interacting with the Company, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**What do we do with the information do we collect?**

At OJCommerce, we always want to provide you with the easiest and best possible shopping experience from the time you begin looking for products and services through the delivery of your requested items. The information that we collect lets us meet this goal by allowing us to: 

  * Customize your shopping experience
  * Confirm, process and track your orders
  * Provide the products and services you request
  * Contact you with questions or status updates regarding an order
  * Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online
  * Fulfill gift card orders
  * Respond to your customer service inquiries or requests
  * Identify your product and service preferences
  * Communicate product promotions, sweepstakes, great values and featured items to you
  * Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
  * Send you OJCommerce email updates
  * Improve our merchandise selection, Website, retail experience and customer service
  * Provide information concerning product recalls or products you have purchased
  * Prevent or mitigate fraud and credit risk
  * Administer billing and payment for your purchases
  * Administer promotions, contests, sweepstakes and rewards programs
  * Comply with applicable law, legal procedures, requirements, regulations and statutes

We collect personally identifiable information (such as first and last name, credit card number, home address, e-mail address and telephone number) that you provide when you make a purchase; create or edit shopping lists; participate in a contest, sweepstakes or other promotion; fill out a survey or questionnaire; sign up for a program or club; contact the Company (by e-mail or otherwise); contact the Company's customer service representative; or otherwise interact with the Company. The information you provide to us may also be combined with demographic and other information that is available in order to allow us to better communicate with you and enhance your shopping experience. For purposes of this policy, information regarding your children that you (the parent) provide to the Company is treated in the same manner as information collected about you. 

**How do we use and share personal information?**

_Using Your Personal Information_

Your personal information is used by the Company to enhance your relationship with us, respond to your requests, tailor offerings to you, communicate with you about products, services, special offerings and events or programs offered by the Company or their marketing partners that may be of interest to you. The Company may also use this information to analyze and manage its businesses. Aggregate data (which does not allow an individual to be identified, contacted or located) is collected from online and offline facilities and may be used to enhance the ability of the Company to communicate with you, and for internal analysis and management purposes.

_Sharing Your Personal Information_

We will not license, sell or provide your personal information to any unaffiliated third party except as permitted by this policy or with your consent. We share your personal information as set forth below: 

_With and between our Brands:_

Personal information collected by one brand of the Company will be used by that brand in accordance with this Privacy Policy and may be shared with other brands of the Company for use only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

_With our Service Providers:_

OJCommerce may share your personal information with service providers who provide services for or administer activities on behalf of the Company (such as, but not limited to, authorization of credit card and check transactions, order fulfillment, sweepstakes and contests, and co-branded or joint product and service promotions). We may share your information with service providers who develop, host or maintain the Sites on behalf of the Company. We may also share your information with service providers who warehouse product, personalize product and perform order fulfillment services on behalf of The Company. These service providers are granted access to some or all of your personal information as necessary and may use cookies (as defined below) on our behalf, but are contractually restricted from using your personal information in any manner other than as may be necessary to perform their services. We may also utilize service providers to assist us in aggregating customer information. We may then share such aggregated information with prospective marketing partners and advertisers.

OJCommerce does offer some of our services in connection with affiliated companies as well as other third parties. Third party websites may have different privacy practices than described in this Privacy Policy. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy policies associated with third party websites as this Privacy Policy applies only to the OJCommerce Website, OJCommerce services, and OJCommerce handling of Personal Information.

Personal Information that you provide to third party websites may be sent to OJCommerce in order to deliver the services you have requested. You can be assured that we will process Personal Information that we receive from these websites in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Each time you visit a Site, the web server automatically collects your internet service provider's address, the web page from which you came, web browser software, and a record of your activity while visiting the site.

_In Connection with Business Transfers:_

In the event that a store, division or part or all of the Company (or the assets of one of those entities) is bought, sold or otherwise transferred, customer information will likely be included among the transferred business assets.

_To Comply with Laws:_

We may also disclose specific information when it determines that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or to protect the interests or safety of its visitors and guests, the Company or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**How do we protect your personal information?**

We use industry standard security techniques on the Sites to help protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected from you at the Sites. When you access your account information or transmit personally identifiable data to the Sites, that information is stored on servers that the Sites have attempted to secure from unauthorized access or intrusion. "Secure Socket Layer" software encrypts all personal information you transmit to the Sites. We cannot be and are not responsible for unauthorized access to information by hackers or others who have obtained such access through illegal measures. 

**What are cookies and how do you use them?**

Our site uses "cookies," which are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The cookies are used to connect your computer with information stored about your preferences and product purchases. (Some examples of this data include your account preferences, items added to your shopping cart, user specific information on pages accessed and previous visits to the site.) We do not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information on your computer. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive new cookies or how to disable cookies altogether. If you reject cookies, you may not be able to participate in certain activities or receive a presentation tailored to you.

**How can I opt out from receiving communications?**

From time to time, you may receive periodic telephone calls, mailings or e-mails from us with information on special promotions, upcoming events, products and services or other offers from us or our marketing partners. You may opt out of receiving e-mail communications by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the e-mail received. It may take us up to 10 days to complete this process, as permitted by law. You may opt out of receiving mailings or telephone calls by completing the online form here. Please note that if you ask us to remove your name from a mailing list, your name will be removed from all of the mailing lists maintained by the Company. In addition, your personal information may be retained in the database for record keeping purposes and for internal research and analysis.

**How can I update or change my personal information?**

You may update or change your personal information by completing the online form here. To change your shipping or billing information for OJCommerce orders, log on, select "My Account" and make the appropriate changes.

**What is the Company's children's privacy policy?**

This Web Site does not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information online, in contravention of these measures, it will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required by law).

**Linked Sites**

OJCommerce.com may contain links to other sites, including content from other sites that is occasionally framed within a Site. Please note that the privacy policies at these other sites may be different from this one. You should review the privacy policy of any site linked to or framed within a Site prior to providing any information on or to that site.

**How to contact us regarding our privacy policy**

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at: [info@ojcommerce.com](mailto:info@ojcommerce.com).
